本字幕由天满宫字幕组制作，翻译:neko，字幕:neko 校对:neko，cinewamage，请在下载后24小时内删除，若因私自传播造成的法律责任，字幕君概不负责。
While kink.com sees its fair share of new models and new sets, it isn't every day
虽然 kink.com 见过许多新模特和新场景，
that a new director walks through the door.
但并不是每天都会有新导演走进门。
But yesterday, the already huge pool of talent that exists at kink.com got a little bit bigger
但是昨天，kink.com 已经存在的庞大人才库迎来了一位新血液
as new director Van Darkholme joined the team.
新的导演范·达克霍姆加入了团队。
So this is Van Darkholme, our new director.
所以这位就是范·达克霍姆，我们的新导演
Hello.
Hey.
And his third day is today.(这句暂未明确，我们选择了最像的这句)
然后今天是他来的第三天
My first day.
我的第一天
First day at school.
我第一天在学校里
Great.
好极了
So uh say hello to him, chat with him when you have a second.
所以先跟他打个招呼，等你有空的时候和他交♂流下。
Thank you.
谢谢
I used to based in Los Angeles, and there was not much of a leather scene down in LA.
我曾经在洛杉矶居住，那里的皮革场景并不是很多。
But I did manage to create a couple.
但我确实设法创建了一对
I do bondage shows for Mr. International Leather Contest.
我为国际皮革大赛做了很多表演。
This is Jason. And Jason is going to be your main PA, I believe.
这是杰森。我相信杰森将是您的主要私人助理。
Hey Jason.
嘿，杰森
Basically, I'm self-taught and, you know, I'm just creating my own unique style of bondage.
基本上，我是自学成才的，你知道，我只是在创造我自己独特的束缚风格。
And now I'm here in San Francisco working for Kink.
现在我在圣佛朗西斯科为Kink工作。
So I'm very, very excited about it. You know, you have no idea.
我对此非常非常兴奋。你知道的，我太激动了
It's like a kid in a candy store. That's what it's like for me.
就像一个孩子在糖果店里一样。这就是我的感觉。
The opportunity to work at Kink.com represents the fulfillment of a dream that Van's had for quite some time.
有机会在Kink.com工作代表着Van长久以来的梦想得以实现。
I saw an article on seven by seven with Peter, and I go, oh my God, that's amazing. I want to
我在seven by seven(日本服饰品牌 品牌名称是他对于旧金山这座城市的昵称，)上看到了一篇关于彼得的文章，我心想，天哪，太惊人了。
work for that man. That was my goal ever since, you know. I made a conscious decision to move up
我想为那个人工作。自从那时起，那就是我的目标。我做出了有意识的决定搬到
to San Francisco, and I sent him an email with my resume, and within the same day, you know,
圣佛朗西斯科，然后给他发了一封带着我的简历的电子邮件，就在同一天，
he got back to me, and I was like, I was impressed. So that's how it happened. With his unique
他回复了我，我很惊讶。所以事情就是这样。
background and impressive body of work everyone at kink.com is excited to see
背景和令人印象深刻的作品，kink.com的每个人都很期待看到
what kind of site van will develop it's bondage gay website it's all male and
凭借Van将开发的这个捆绑同性恋网站是什么样的。
it's a little bit for everybody you know we're gonna bring in experienced players
这是一个全男性的网站，适合各种人，我们将邀请经验丰富的SM和捆绑玩家，
in SM and bondage and also we also welcome first-timers I want to get you
同时也欢迎新手。我想要吸引各种不同类型的人，
know all different types you know the the skinhead leather tattoo piercing
比如光头皮革纹身穿孔的人，
types and I also want to bring the boy next door. The main theme is everybody's
同时也想要邻家男孩。主题是每个人
getting tied up whether they like it or not. That's the main theme and hot sex.
都会被束缚，不管他们喜不喜欢。这就是主题，还有热辣的性爱。
You know I came here when I was 10 and landed right in the Midwest. You know so
你知道我十岁时来到这里，直接落地在中西部。
I was a farm boy all my life. All that small-town American stuff. So I spent
所以我一生都是个农场男孩。所有那些美国小镇的东西。
most of my time in the barn creating fantasies so now I'm putting them to
所以我大部分时间都在谷仓里创造幻想，现在我正在把它们
good use. Having been searching for someone to help them break into the gay
好好利用起来。在寻找帮助他们进入同性恋
market for over a year, Kink.com is thrilled to finally have Van on the team.
市场的人员已经超过一年之久后，Kink.com 终于很高兴地将 Van 加入团队。
With his extensive experience, fresh perspective, and unflagging focus and
凭借他丰富的经验、新颖的视角以及
energy, Van Darkholme is a welcomed addition to the Kinky family.
坚定的专注和活力，范·达克霍姆是Kinky家族中备受欢迎的新成员。